Hello everybody and that's like there we will talk about
Flashlight design pattern is provide a unified interface to set off interfaces
Define higher level interface
That makes the subsystem easier to us
Last year was that simple example
Complex subsystem for operating at home theater
That might be individual components like amplifier
DVD player projector Etc
Instead of having the client code
Interact with each component separately
Just like the interaction
Here's
We can call
First the latest the Fine Art Classes we have a amplifier okay
On the amplifier last I have some metals less implement the methods
We have a public what is on the method and is on method we are simulating the behavior
We are like the others
Is consolidate right line
Amplifier
Amplifier is on
Okay then we have another one let's make this uppercase
It has the best practice
Employment last three
Three method for
Second I want to set set volume
On this set volume is setting volume
So let's say
Let's get that level here
Because we are setting
Hello star
I like to say we have
Setting volume
While we are setting volume
We are setting volume
Okay and the last one is amplifier
Instead of on off and let's say amplifier is off
Okay I'll let you set seconds left to say
Play we have a tuna antenna has let's say
Set
Setting the air mode
Setting
Unless I said
FM
Setting to
And I want to put another subsystem and let's say I have a DVD
Higher for my home theater and that's where the player was saying the play
How's the weather player has some meds like
Let me copypastas let's go for me
We have our own method DVD player
DVD
DVD player is on
Play Method play methods
Play let's say also giving the instead of integer level I am giving strange movie
And I am putting that here
I'm playing classic playing movie
Another one that says stop I have a stop method in nobody player
Let's call it
Stopping movie
Let's say we have some
Extra two metals one is eject
Ejecting
We have off methods
TV repair yes off okay
Let's cry the last one and I want to call it as
Projector project I have a projector
Like this one I want to set the old method for my projector and projector is on
What did I say projector is on
I have LLC input DVD
And there's a setting in
And I have another one and it is off
On projector is let's say off
Okay
Do we have one to 344 subsystem and import
I'm trying to we have a perfect pattern here
And what's that say our first sight pattern has class home
Theaters
Theater website okay and there's home theater First Sight is
Have I amplifier right we have amplifier for our system
On this one we have at dinner
Also we have a DVD player
And also we have a projector right
Turn off
Last
The away
Players and let's say projector
Okay we have are all
Stop systems in our home theater facade
Let's create a public Constructor for us home
Better flashlight
Let's say we have amp
We need all of them right
Amplifier
A&P
And then turn off Sooners MP I want to use
Lowercase is off cars turn off okay I have
DVD player Radio Player okay
Can I have a project and of course I have to
Make them
Let me to the up again
I want to yes I know of them and people say MP
How about 10 or as the vehicle tuners okay I have deal with the players
And also the projector right and this has to be with the play
Hush oh my gosh yes they were the players and I also have a projector here
I'm done
Lettuce implement
Mathis
Faucet
Clash Royale what can be done
Okay parsley let's say we have a watch movie right at
Turn off the day if we have
Home theater
We have to do that for
Watching movies
Because of that I need that watch movie meth
I want to watch me when your mother's last second so that right line
No the right light
Bright light
Get ready
To watch movie right
Add some Dots here
What we have to do watch movie
We have before sleepy amplifier all right
Dad must say we are setting amp
Set volume we need some volume to watch movie
Let's say I am
Assigning tuner to set
FM right we need that for that
We need to open our DVD
On
The weather play
Do you have any player dots
All right I have to on my DVD player
And
I have to say DVD
Play
Play right we have a Playmobil to play the movie
I have to say projectors
Dot I have to open my projector
On the last one maybe
Projectors
Start DVD
Input DVD
Our projector getting the movie from the input already
Pablo
Boys
And also let me say
Methods
But in this time
I am projector firstly let's say
We are making the similar things but in the river or the right instead of projector on I have
What's the projector off
Anita's to be first one right I am projector off and after that
Let's say I am
The radio stop method DVD player
Let me
There's one to last
On projector off is finished
We have
Handle DVD things
Do the player Farsi last a DVD player stop I am stopping my
I'm done
DVD player dots
I have to eject my city or they already
And that I am closing my DVD player
Weather of method
I'm
I am amplifier off
Yeah it is the basically how you can and a movie right and that
I am riding my client quote I have an amplifier
AMPM equals new amplifier
I am
Okay
Amplifier
DVD players
Let's call it is there already and it tells you they already players
And I have a projector in my home theater and it is projector has to be new
Projector
And then I am creating Katie at home
Theater faces
Theater first aid
Flashlight
Seattle last day I need us to be
Near Home Theater 5
And I have to give all of them
What are the amp
Parsley amp
DVD
On projector I guess all of them is that
Okay we created our first date or sorry our theater and I only want
Watch me away last day
Inception okay
I'm
After watch that I want to end movie
Nightmare on my coat
Okay did you see
We are ready to watch movie amplifier is on setting volume to five setting FM
Activate the players on playing Inception project result
Setting up input DVD and get ready to watch movie projector is off
Oh my
Shutting down the music
Down the movie
Shutting down movie theater project results stopping movie ejecting movie theater players off and amplifier
Airtel how you can use this far side powder the basically
Simplify the complex of setting up a movie instead of manually turning on each component
The first aid provide simple must
Watch movie online movie the client in the case
On the interacts with the flashlight button right we are not putting all this card into
It is giving us very very good
Abstraction and this is how you can use this as a pattern for a home theater
You have to
Instead of cancel that right now you have to give Tom
Call Montoya the player playing USANA
Complex logic about basically we are similar to behavior and this is how you can do it thank you