How old is Harry Potter
Arrow
Add three and more
At how branches and leaves combined from a complex
That's beautiful structure
Today we are going to Encore programming concept that mirrors this natural water
The composite
Design pattern
Let's look at what's composite Pat
Let's go back to our tree
You can observe it as a whole or you could zoom in on individual brands
However
A general interact with all of them
Using the same set of
Operations
You water the tree
Not eat
In the weather
The composite pattern allows us to do something similar
Is lots of stride individual objection compositions of objects
In the family
Let's talk about the characteristics
The composite pattern has distinguishing
Character
Primarily
Simplifies the client called by allowing to interact
Individual OB
And compositions
In a uniform matter
It's just
You won't care for the
Not for easily
Is organizes objects into three structures
Trip
Park hall heer
It's much like the tree itself is a structure composed of branch
Richard damsels
Composed of smaller branches
Let's talk about
Is Andrew
Like every design pattern
The composite pattern has it has advantages
And also pitfall
Simpl
The comp
What's Patron simplifies the client called
Buy a lion get to interact with individual objects and their compositions
In a sandwich
Much like you won't
For a whole tree
Or a sing
Ease of adding new component
Where's the compass pattern
Components to the system
It's just like the straightforward to add a new Branch or a
Track
However
Not all that glitches is gold
Design
Complex
The composite pattern can make your design more complex
Bite introduc
Many additional classes
Just as a
Time became
Complicated
What's with many branches
On
Second
Difficulty in restaurants
In composite pattern
It can be difficult to restrict the types of components
As a composite can how
It's just as it's hard to limit what type of leaf a branch can beer
Let's talk about the US Kansas
When will it be applied to composite Pat
Let's Branch out from our tree anal
Just as you would use that tree to present a biology
Hierarchy the composite pattern is useful
Why you want to represent
Hierarch
Your system
When you want to trade individual
And composite object
It's just like you
You water
The entire tree are not easily separately
The composite pattern is Handy why you want your client called to trade individual
Encompassed object
Uniform
Us
Just that tree is composed of
Smaller branches on lay
Graphic user interfaces of
Involve complex nesting of different types of
Useful tool for
F*** you development
File system
Structure represents directions contain
You know files or other directories
The composite pattern is very used in the
Designing an interacting with file systems
Our first one the runner
Three dimensional object
Is in graphic artists were composed objects can be built from primitive shapes the composite
Pattern is used to simplify the
Processing John manipulation of the escapists
Do we have
An organic understanding of
Like a
In your backyard it's a natural and essential tool in your design pattern mask
Is simplifying your interaction
Complex objects structures
If you have got any questions
Feel free to drop
In the questions and ask for
I am here
Assist you
Are finding the course benefic
Play Levi radio
Your feedback is the water and sunlight
That Nour
What's better contact
There's a whole Forest of knowledge
To the Explorer and you definitely
Thanks for your time today for
Cheap clothing
Keep growing
Add Syria
Next