Hello everybody in those like your we will talk about composite design pattern
The compost design patterns that structural pattern that composes objects into three
Poop
Hall hierarchy
There is Alice clients to trade individual objects and compositions of objects uniformly
Last take the example of graphics
Imagine you have basic shapes like circles
Add rectangles
And you also want to group this shapes into more complex drawings
Here's how you can implement
Compose pattern for Less
Enterprise
I graphic interface we have
I'm
Let's say it has to
Abstract method troll
Andrew employment
We have leave notes
And the leaf notes last say we have a public class
Charcoal on it as a graphic
Graph
Okay
We have a public Wyatt draw
We have to implement public withdraw and you will see at the value of an arrow
Why is because we have to implement all of the interfaces
We have public lawyer draw here
And there's sorry what I am doing where I am only simulating the behavior so
Drawing circle
And then will I say we have another one
Add as an hourly and it has public class
Pause the rectangle
And there's rectangle inheriting for my graphic
We have seen implement this one again right
Public radio on instead of driving Circle
I want to implement another one and I want to call
Broadcast
No I will not come
Make that bigger I will
Implement the composite pattern here we have to implement composite
Will I say we have a public class
Composite graphic graphic
It is inheriting from Minecraft
I'm done we come into Cape Point what is our Cape Point
We have we are we have a private read only variable here for sleep
It is keeping list
Coffee
And we are calling some graphics right
Start them as new list tiger fish
I'm done I have a matter of public works at
Today's one public right at and it is getting a graphic
Garage
Okay
Crawfish
You are I guess you
Alrighty gas
What will do we will add graphics to
There's graphic
If we have ADD we need remote right
Remove
I am having to remove here
I'm done
It has to be remove alarm
I guess this has to be uppercase by the way
I am remember
Like
Yeah it has to be
Are Park
Why is young girl
Call Anthony
System
Okay I am driving time from the reference
Why it does not suggesting that
Music
Can you remind it
What is the last Library
I guess it has to be system
It has to be in collections
That's correct
It has to be in January
And you know you know we need to implement public with robot we will make another
Nothing here
Can you start off
Ride line that one I am using for each
Wow girl face
Graph
In graphics right
Graphics
And I will print all of them
Cancel that right line
Okay we have canceled out right now in the graphics of each I am
Graph
Start throwing
And then we have to implement
Public white method for our client called
Let's create individual objects for how we can do that
We have to create I graphic
Circle for example it has to be in your circle right
I say we have another one instead of circle I am creating a rectangle
Rectangle on it has to be rectangle right
I'm done we have creating composite objects last composites
Graphics last great composite graphics
Unless call Denise Graphics one on
Composite graphical
Composite graphic and composite graphic okay
And then I am adding this Graphics one to add
Add this
Circle Forest
What's the problem
I need to ask a garage on Google
Let's say we are creating another one like that
Is that of Graphics 1 I am crazy Graphics 2
On the graphics to last ads are composite Graphics directly here
Okay
Because still it is
Let me add another one I am trying to
Troyer's case
Last call graphics
To the throne message
Traffic
Call Martha did you see throwing circular rectangular Circle
Wait there's one we are growing old Graphics implants composite let me explain
And maybe we will talk it again
Parsley
Do we have a i graphics
Andy's I graphic is the component in french fries
All the graphic objects
It can be simple or composite
Employment test
Where did you find that for this
We have a circle
And these are the lymph
Graphics that can be drawn right
We have a composite graphic here
It is the composite object and that can store and manage child graphics
Turn on Starbucks simple Graphics like circus and rectangles
Another composite Graphics to enabling the creation of complex structures
Volume 100% individual graphics
Group them into compost graphics and then draw everything
The beat of compost pattern is that
The client doesn't need to differentiate between simple
Like
On composite like this
Everything is Straight Talk's uniformly and this is how we can implement it
How does a complex structure but my understanding you can
Behave everything like your eye graphic it can be a graphics composite graphic but you can
Use it like that