Hello again my name is to dance
On the previous director way in Plymouth where basic composite pattern
As like shape
But in the lecture we will make
Add more complex in real life one it
At Classic
File organizational file system using directories on files if you will be
Play familiar with that because you are using it in everywhere in computer science
And let's look at that
NFL system
Wall by rectory
Folder sound files can be seen as items right
We have followers and also files
Why are you a lullaby is a basic item that can't contain other items right
They are saying if it's a fire you can't
Put A Fire Inside the Fire you can put to that in
Add folder or directory
I need a directory can contain both files and other directors right and this nested
What is nature model music composed pattern
Weekend model is using compost pattern like last instead of I graphic
Call let's call it
File system
What's simulate a file with only public string name
And I am also putting together shutters here
God set
And also
That is my
Uppercase because it has the best practice and done
Quiet are public
What is
The name of that we are creating the Constructor
Off a file let's call string name and last assignment into
What's his name okay
And then let's
Play every
File system item
That's correct
Instance Constructors
What's that mean
Okay let's continue I guess it will disappear we have an abstract Mets here
Let's call it is display to display a file
Or maybe directory
That's at indentation
I will seem like the behavior I am getting indentation
Valentine what does what
I am defining this as a class it is giving care of because of that
I'm giving abstract metal so it has to abstract clause
Is also calling Jazz Enterprise by the way if you
Have some trouble to understand this one with the public interface maybe I can put
Small text about that or small video
But if you want please
That as a question or
Let's find me
I'm done we have a listeners right
We have at last
Public class or class file
And I am in hurting from file system item
Let me call that
File system item it will ask me
Create public file contractor laser string
And I am going to base namir
It is another creation of that one and I have to
All right
White display okay on the way this play has to get integer
An indentation
Don't worry about this usage my I printed you will understand
What does play let me write console about right line
Let's say a new strange
Slash invitation
Last name
Expect
Call
What's the problem
Play Spotify
Okay this is another method if you can to add public you have to add in Waldorf
If you didn't like that it's also possible you can make that is private
Set that private
But that's
Maybe
We don't need to ride public again and again
I don't like this one instead of file I am creating another one I am calling you directory
I need to ask the directory name has to be named
We need another things here like
Composite right
You can't think there's a composite graphics
It is nearly sandwich at 1:00 let me add tomatoes like that
Farsi we have this one okay
It has to be a file system item file system item
Is that of graphics
Let's call it items
I need this too also
Instead of items items this has to be file system item file system
Let's call it item item
Item item okay
We need this play right
Endangering temptation
That is why I will do that
By the
Instead of graphics
I will call it item and items
Item that's display
Just play
Every time I am doing invitation + 2
It has to work
Okay
You will understand why I'm using this logic it is allergic to print
System main God we have a fight let's say we have a final one and it is near file
File one of the txt okay unless that means a file
Because Danielle file fire fire fire fire to
DxD okay and we have at least a war
Reliable subdirectory and it is near directory
Andy's new director is sup let's call it soft director
Okay and then I have some let me at this subdirectory
Let me add directly a new file in here I want to show all
Different use cases
Txt
Okay
I'm done
I am creating a reliable Route 3 and it is
Call Saul has to be a new directory and I am calling it Road
On let me fix some of the errors firstly
Software one DxD we need another close parenthesis here
Let me add this road directory to my old files
Stop at file one
Fire alarm okay
I'm also adding other
Two things here
File to and also adding the subject ready Road directory
I am only saying what road directory
Let's play okay and I am giving initially in Plantation as well
Lattice see what we will
We have Sapphire one txt
Also you can add more like
Sapphire to Sapphire tree
Let's run it
Did you see we have
File at the
And we have three in the shop
Director
I want to explain quote one by one
Or let me make a simple explanation we see that directory composite
Play Tank on
And money manage multiple file system item right
What's going to be the file I leave not or even another directory and one minutes away the root directory
It regardless of the display is all of it is contacts and illustrating the power of compost
Modeling Harajuku structures
This is how you can Implement a file system