How old are
You know what colors
Happy hour the correct that Christmas tree
Start with
Play country on
Add up
Ornaments and cancel until you had something entirely faster and
Does the idea we are going to turn up today in
Programming r
What's the decorative person
Think about that Christmas tree again
You start with something simple
And gradually layer on
Transforming it into something different and more complex
The Decorator pattern allows us to do something similar with
Are object
Where is start with a bicycle object and then add on decorator
What's the accent is functionality
What's wrong time
Without altering the object structure
Set let's talk about the characteristics
The Decorator pattern has distinct features
Allows us to add a new responsibilities
Turn up
Where is dynamic
Is just like getting decorations to Christmas tree
Is provides a flexible alternative to stop closing for
Extending functional
To how you can change the appearance of a
Let's talk about benefit
And also that are all
Like a beautiful decorated Christmas tree
Patterns comes with is
And also
More flexible than static inherit
The Decorator pattern provide some more
Flexible
It's right to add responsible to stop
That can be hard with
Compile time
Inheritance
Add similar to
How you can easily change the decorations on a
Second
Complex
What did the creator of Pat
We cannot functional to
Object
Is without affecting other objects
Avoid
An oral complicated
It's like subclass in hierarch
That is not always Jingle Bells right
It can cause
Problems
First
Tell it to many small classes
You know
How many Truman decorations can make a tree a low cardiac
The decorate your pattern can lead to system
With lots of similar-looking
Small class
It can be hard to keep track
Decorator and their component
Aren't I
I like it
Is decorations
Decorative aren't identical to objects that the
Which can you know complicate Court maintenance
And also understanding
Let's talk about the news
When should we employed decorator pattern
Let's stick with our Christmas tree analog
Parsley
Add responsibilities dynamically
Just like adding decorations to a tree
Responsibilities to an object
Dynamically and transparently
Pet
Affecting other OB
Second
One extending functionality
Just as you can change your trees time each year
By changing the decorations
The decorating pattern is useful
When you need to extend the functionality
How far single object
But without impacting other instances
What's on Santa
Graph
Enterprise Focus
Is much like you can decorate a tree with different combinations of decorations
Using this decorator pattern to add properties
Borders or behaviors
What's scrolling to a window
Let's say input output
The Decorator pattern is used extensively in
Are other languages input output class like
In the Java bathroom
These are the essential
Decoration that provide useful additional features
Middleware function
For example in JavaScript Express jazz
Can be seen as decorators
That's modify http
Or responds
And that wraps up our understanding of decorator pattern
Is much like a beautiful decorative tree it's powerful
Two in your design pattern Arsenal
Is providing
Music features they are object
If you have got any questions
Put them into the questions and ask for section
I am here
To assist you
If you are finding the call Spanish
Please
Levi review
Aura writing
Your feedback is the star on top of our contact 3
Don't stop here
There's an entire Christmas Market of knowledge
To the Explorer
And you surely
Don't want to message
Thanks for joining me today folks
Keep quiet
Skip the question
And see you
Our next lesson