Hello everybody in this lecture we will talk about decorative pattern
It's a structural design pattern
Dad that loves you to add new functionalities to existing objects
Altering the structure
The pattern in Moses set of decorator class
Strap concrete components
Decorator classes near the type of components they decorate
But add or override Behavior
Let's imagine
You have a simple coffee ordering system and you want to be able to extend the system
To handle the various add-ons like my
Sugar
Whipped cream
And without modifying the original coffee color
Let's break it down
Translate
I'm putting Jack explanation for our system we have a component
Another component is
Coffee
I'd like to say this coffee class this is the main
Object
Which you
To add some responsibility
Dynamically
Concrete
Component
Another concrete component is simple coffee
What's a simple coffee
On this simple coffee let's call it this is an
Concrete object
Will be decorating
Are we having another one and it is decorator let's call that is the call
Brighter
On this decorator let's say this is an abstract
Claws
Top Colossus
The components
Is the base
Far less
Concrete
Decorators okay
We have concrete decorator you know the concrete means the
Lamentation of
Bass class right abstract class
We last say we have milk decorator
Let's say we have another one sugar decorator
Maybe extra shot decorate respect her and these are
Did that quieter
Decorator
Stop Colossus
That's at
Functionalities
To the components
Step one is
Coffee right let's Implement that probably abstract we say this abstract
Buy the abstract class coffee
And there's abstract class coffee is basically
How do I say two abstract methods and first one is public abstract
Double cost okay
Add this returning to cost and I want to make it upper case
Can we have another one it is also abstract method we will all right thumb
Let's say description
4r
Description
Coffee
The second step is creating implementing the concrete comp
Turn on and we call that a simple copyright
Close simple coffee
Coffee
It is
Inheriting from coffee
If we inheriting from coffee we have to override the
That's one right probably all right
Let's say double cost
And this double cost is basically making some job like
Return five okay
Call last call it is base cost for coffee with Define the
Adults it is five
Dollar
Paulie Colorado description string Des
Kitchen and our description is basically returning simple
Coffee okay
On after the description it has to be description
Implantation simple coffee
Coffee description gas
It will be disappear I guess
On the
Tri is implemented
Implementing The Decorator
Less implant
Does public we are implementing the abstract class right abstract
Pause are abstract class is coffee
The Creator and his coffee decorator is inheriting from coffee
We are important for my base
Abstract class car for decorator let's take this is protected coffee
We have a coffee
We will decor
And we are assigning does as coffee
Coffee okay
We have
Coffee decorators
Constructor and coffee decorator Constructor getting coffee as
Coffee
On assigning that into our
Protect its reliable
Coffee equals coffee
And we have the Implement to other methods last Implement that like this one
We we have an abstract so we have to do
Coffee coffee we have to say
Pause the abstract public abstract
But we are overriding the base
All
And we are overriding device right
Okay what's the problem
Call the font
Coffee
Okay everything looks good we need to implement our concrete decorators right
Concrete decorators
Let's say we have a public
Male the corridor and our milk decorators inheriting from of course the coffee
Decorate to our base is coffee decorator
On in the mail decorator
We have to
Employment
What's Publix
The contractor milk decorator and we have to
Coffee as a coffee
And there's coffee as a coffee you died into our coffee class
Constructor
What does one line Constructor implementation by the way
I'm done
I guess we don't need that
Make the corrector
Coffee coffee base coffee okay I guess it will be this is a parallel song that's probably
Double
Cost meth
But we have a difference here
The differences
What's the problem
Coffee
We have a difference here while you're riding
We have to say it is a decorator right we have to say coffee
Stop
Let's say if we are adding a milk to in our coffee we are adding cost to
And also in description
We are
Returning
Coffee
Description
We got this description
Wet let's call
Lights out that comma here on wet milk here okay
Did you see
Cost is increased one and we at Dez
Add wet milk
In the
Time
That's not enough
And also I am adding a sugar decorator
Let's say sugar decorator
Add sugar decorator and there's caused us to be like that with sugar
Did you
Basically and I can also add other ones where it is really
Basically let me write
Call and let me explain
Are Klein cotton nutmegs playing it after finish last day we have a coffee and we
Calling his simple coffee
On the simple coffee is basically simple coffee right we have
Clothes like that
On this simple coffee
After the simple coffee we have our last console that right line
Red
I am saying
Simple latest simple
Are simple coffee
Stop description for sale
Let's say
How do you make that simple coffee description
Also let me put my simple coffee
Cost
Coffee
I guess it will be enough for us
I'm done I decided to create a meet coffee
I want to add milk
My coffee
How can I do that
Firstly I have to define a coffee make coffee
But I don't need to create a new class for this milk coffee
I only need to say
New
Make that quieter
I said that Creator and I have to give my
Simple coffee to my milk decorator and it will handle all the jobs
On I am printing
Okay
Play anything meet coffee
And also I decided to add sugar to my make coffee how can I do that it is very
I am adding sugar
I want a sugar coffee instead of meat decorator I am using sugar decorator but
I am directly changing them I am adding milk and then sugar and the sugar coffee
And run
Okay that's perfect
It's working in fast
Did you see at the beginning we have a simple coffee and our cost is five right
I'm done
I decided to add a simple coffee with milk I decided that milk to my coffee and it
Play Star Wars currently and I add sugar and $7 currently
Let me explain
And then we can decorate simple coffee object with additional features like me or Sugar by rap
Can you recite the milk decorator
Total cost of the coffee
Play and the weather like right there you can easily add or remove responsibilities from objects
Dynamically right did you see we are making them dynamically
You can extend the coffee ordering system with new ads on sweetheart changing car coffee and
Can you put coffee Colossus and this is how you can Implement that coffee