Hello everybody
Simulate
A middleware pipeline
Asp.net core
That includes login
Cashing
Anna Plantation behaviors
This will not be an actual round about asp.net core application
Bob the Builder demonstrated decorator Concept in a middleware contacts
Last Ride
Parsley
Wake me at my using I am adding another reason I will use system collection
Generic
System
Call actions
Directions
Generic and also I will use Trading
Nothing system
Trading
Tasks okay
I'm done
I have a public interface I request it is keep
Is my request to my alarm for 12:00
Process
I'm done
I have a basic request and it has
Concrete
Play implementation of this I request let's make that
I have a public class basic request last day and it is
Inheriting from I request and because of that I have to
Probably I have I have to implement probably
Process
As only add a console
That's right line
I have to write line
Processing basic request okay
Requ
And this processing basic request done
Knock knock
I'm done
I am implementing a public abstract base
Public abstract class it is
Let's call it Middle where
Decorator
And if you are not familiar with metal wears
Play
Ask that as a question or
Inform me
Protect us
And I can put that small documentar
Video for what is
On my request
Request
I'm done I am
Friday's public
Middle layer decorator Constructor
And I request
Request
I request request
I'm done
I am writing
I am assigning my request into this request
We have to
I am not implementing this or riding public abstract White
Process and the concrete wall swell handle
Okay we Implement our middleweight decorator and last credit card decorator first
I decided to
Walking
Into my
Request with my decorator how can I do that I only need to probably close
Logging
Middle
Where Anita has to be middleware
Weather weather
My corrector what we have to do
Parsley we have to give
Constructor and there's Loggins middleware decorator have to get this
Request request
And we have to pass that into our Base Class request
And then we can finish that
Okay we are training so I always
Put that into bass and that we have to public
All right
Play Wyatt last say process right
On this process is basically made the console
Not right line
What will do logging
Request okay
I'm done I have to call my
Request that process right
I completed adding logging middleware
In the future I decided to add cashing to my request with middleware and I am
I'm adding cashing metal wire
Cashing middleware and it has to be cashing middleware in the process
Best implemented Behavior at better less at the private
Static
Are dictionary
String string okay
And I am using cash and
This cash has to be
What has to be near dictionary string string right I am creating any additional strength strength
And
In the process I am falsely checking
Are cash
Contains
Right we have a dictionary and I am going to
Let's say I am using KKR here
On the k i
Say
Console that rightline
Fetching from the cash and
And I am
Returning
Okay I catched from the cash and return this value I don't need to process my request
Otherwise
I have to request process to request
I'm done I have to ask this in this case Into Cash
I am using hardcore strings of cars
Otherwise it has to be get from the request value
I decided to
Authentication middleware I decided to add authentication to my API
And I am calling that
I am I don't need this cashing mechanism
The important
Point here is process right we don't have a cash anymore
In the function at
I am saying
Console
Spotlight
Let's say authenticating
The organic I think the request
Okay
I'm done
I am assigning care what I believe is all time
Ticket office and
Real case scenario it will be
Request
Where are some lighting Behavior
IMs I think that that's true so
If it's authenticated
Of course it is that
Unusable cold spot
We are simulating the behaviors for
Don't worry about that
Is that if it is a quad
What time does we are request that process right
We don't have any problem with that
But otherwise
I have a console that right light
Authentication failure
I'm done
Are function is finished that is right or client called and explain it that
We have a I request right
I request we will make a request
Oh my gosh I request request
I am starting creating a basic
Requests we already implanted that
Okay
I'm done
I am adding request to a menu middleware I am adding
Logging
Into my
Request
And then I decided that my request to new
Can you start off logging
Decided that cashing
And after that I decided to
I decided not to add
Authentication
Authentication middleware
I'm done I am saying
This is my API on I am saying process this request
Let's see what will happen
Compilation Arrow oh my gosh what is the problem with that
Request process Publix at 4
Last
Still have a problem if I was public with public cloud
Okay we completed the writing we have authentication request first logging and processing
Can I buy a zebra Quest these are all
First let's make a quick explanation
Quick explanation
We have a basic request this represent our basic request handling
We have a decorator middleware logs and cashing on authentication right
On the program class setup the login cashing Authentication
Thumb process the request
On the process method in each middleware either continues to the next middleware
Or stop the processing based on conditions right
We have a cashing we don't have any problem but if you have an authentication problem we are not continue the process
That's right we are stopping on Chromecast here
On the process and this
Captures the essence of how medal wears work in real life applications
And simplified manner
And the most of the Frameworks like that that's actually a lot of them already implement
You are only using dump
But the logic behind them is
And this is very common use case
This Pat