Hello everybody and I was like there we will implement
Another very common use case of abstract Factory pattern for
Document
Chang
Imaginext simplified scenario where are program deals with two kinds of
Come on last say
Document a
On PDFs
Is document format last day has two elements we have a text and also the image
Add last design the abstract Factory Pat
For
Let's start writing your caught with
Abstract proluxe Write the basic
Implementation mostly right starting point
Abstract products and
Off the application it does system by the way
We are dealing with different kind of documents in lots of systems and
Very common use case
Does abstract Factor pattern here
We have a high tax document
What say it is returning to where this play
Display text
If you want
You think
Do you think real example for example for that we are making some prints and
They are simulating the behavior
Oh by the way always use that
I am using that one
To make the scars using
Structures
Unless the abstract products again and public interface
I text Andy's I text
Returning sorry not returning
The interface abstract Methodist display text
We have another interface
Oh by the way if you want to make this real
Please
Asking questions and answer or request them directly to me and I can maybe implement
Kill the one with real
I text an images
And you can't see how you can make it real it is a simulating
The behavior
I need instead of display text you most probably
Cast display image rights
Okay
We have to you know after we cried the abstract products
We are creating
Concrete products right
Concrete
Products
If you don't know the meaning of concrete I put a document for that period
Aerial dance or miss that please read it public class
Let's say
Documents
Text
Document X
Text and you know it is a concrete product we have to
Inherit from
Abstract one and it is giving you all because we have to implement display
The less implemented display
Text
You know we have to make it public by the way
Public wire display text and the display text
Let's say
Cancel that right line also another syntax is very commonly using for one line
Function says that
You can directly
Cancel that
Brightline here and you can say
Displaying
Dog eggs text
Text
And after doing after that
What is the problem
Expected
Oh my gosh
Why you are not expect you don't have to expect that
Bright light consolidate line
Okay let me write the second one
Okay yes fixing Caledon right now
EMH and everything is an image we have to get from this displaying topics
Amazon this has to be displayed image right
And you know we have the kids and dog cakes and we let's say a little later
Where we got that PD
We have SIMPLE amount of PDF one
What's a PDF image
P
Let's
Some consistent farting that I am using
Uppercase
Okay and this has to be PDF right
Oh my gosh we changed the wrong one
Let me take time
Let's make that PDF
And this has to be PDF also
After this we have to
Create or abstract Factory right did you see the pattern we are first in the abstract products
For this products we are concrete we have concrete products
And after concrete products the last step is
Abstract Factory it is how you can implement
You can't think that like a blueprint for abstract Factory pattern
Let's Implement our interface public interface
Let's say I we have a i document
Factory
Let's do that
These are the document Factory need to implement
Sorry
Near
Thanks right we have a great text
And also I image
I text an image
Let's call it crate
Image
We have an interface when it's two metals to implement that
After abstract Factory
You know we have an abstract one we need the concrete once concrete
Victorious
You already
Understand
What is the concrete products we need public class
We need that
Document X Factory right
Factory
You know we have to
Inherit from this one and this will give error because we didn't implement
Abstract Metals right we need to implement them
When is the Implement that also
And this has to be
Public also right
And this has to return
Let's use this in Texas again
For either human factor a doggy Factory I have to return near dog is tax
And for other one I have to return
It has to be a public also
New dog
Image right
Okay after we create
Turkish Factory video also need to implement
Pedia Factory right if this is PDF
This is also need to be a PDF right
PDF text and this has to I text okay we need PDF tax PD
It's not a text man PDF text
After that let's create our client instead of writing conference program
I think our clients
On this client is probably class let's call it as
Documents
Avatar
Are decimeters are Clive and there's really
This was on you know we can
Take
As read only pry
I text we have
Bright and let's call it no no no no no no no no no I text has to be
Let's call it as fast not
It has to be text
On another one private read only
An image has to be image
Done
I will ask you factory here we have a public
Contractor here right we need public document editor and his document edit
Start getting high documents
Factory
As a parameter and it will
USC what people said most probably
If you don't we have a taxi cost
538 text right
5:30
Create text
Another one has to be
530 dots
Image
Has to be
Create a meteorite
Okay
Wait on the alarm
For testing was that public Wyatt
Display
Contacts
This display contacts
That's basically
What is making does a text start
Display text
Contacts has to be
Count right yeah
It has to be display text right
Images TV
Display image
We completed implementation of our document Factory
Let's say
We have to use it
In our main function I need the eye document Factory right
Factory has to be dark is Factory right and it has to be
Dog is Factory right
We need that documentary here
Hi document Factory we need a document editor
On this document editor let's call it dog is a guitar
Add attorneys by the right
What we have to do we only need to near
Document editor
32 months
What is the human temperature
And we have to give our dog is Factory
That is a problem man
Dog eats Edgar
Has to display contents right
And you most probably already
Gas
Let's write it instead of that one I am creating PDF one
And it has to be PDF and this has to be PDF also right and
This has to be pedia Factory
We have to say PDF
Edgar
Is that type which is not about given contact
Unless
At that we
Ed Sheeran
Implementing
Abstract Factory pattern in document after right let's look at
We have abstract products
And these are General interfaces for text and image
We have concrete products
And these are the specific implementation of toxic son PDF
Formats of this abstract products we have an abstract Factory here
Does abstract Factory provides the method
That's a signatures for creating text on image right
I'm done we have concrete factories and these are the real deal factories
This is donkeys Factory pops up the kids products and PDF Factory
Is for PDF
On the climb the decrement that is our class show cases that has document
Pause where is the documented star
Okay it says here the document that is your class showcases how one might use this
Depending on the factory password
Using the Quality Inn the main function with instantiate Factory is for both
Play cakes on PD
Dash of their contacts
Run it on
How
Don't worry about the
530 pattern use cases and maybe in the future you have another format
And what you have to do you don't need to change document editor or you don't need to change previous
Let's
PDF Factory
Instead of
There's one that say we have another one
We have another format PDF
For example Maybe
And you have to do that like this
And you have to create a factory for that and
On the adding the necessary Alliance
You update your call then it will run
Without any new
Changes on the previous ones and this is how you can implement
Document Factory
Start Netflix
Abstract Factory pattern