Hello everybody
Beaver Explorer have fun scenario using the abstract Factory pattern for
Video games
Suppose we are working with a game that will open company
And that produces games
For different platforms
Like you can't think the platforms like
PC
Cancel it can be passed station or Xbox or any other console
Mobile games
And you
Its platform has this thing characteristics wise
We have controls
The way the player interacts with the game it can be cable that much it can be
Also touch screen
We have Graphics right
The type of Graphics the platform support
Maybe higher resolution maybe it's standard
Resolution
And we have song
On the sound quality on FX for each platform it can be stereo sound or mon
Add last represent the characteristics using
Abstract Factory pattern
You know why we are doing this we are starting with our abstract products
Sorry abstract products
While doing abstract products we have
I control
Public interface we have
I controls
And you know I controls
Of course I will not implement the whole control structure but
Simulate the behavior we have I control yet control
Time and you know I mentioned we have different controls
Kmart on Mars concert
We have public interface for
I Graphics right are I Graphics can be last night
Strange you are a retard the graphics card
Graphics
Girl
He's quality
You know we have the last one and it is public interface
What is that we need a song
And there's ice songs
Basically returning spring on it
Sound quality let's call it as quality
Thanks for I controls but we are simulating Behavior
After the abstract products
You actually need
Concrete products concrete
Concrete products
And our concrete products can be PC controls PC graphics PC salt
Last employment on public
Public
No pop
I can't write public sorry
Public class
Contrast right
Can we have to inherit from I controls
After that it will give an error because you didn't Implement I controls
Control type
How we can do that
We have to say public strength unless they get
Control
Type yes let me copy paste for Airways the common
Some steak and I am returning keyboard
And mouse for computer okay
I have to do that for other two abstract methods right
We
Biographics we have icons
Instead of controls we need to say
Graphics
PC graphics
You need to say PC sound
And we need to
I found PC songs instead of
We have to I Graphics need to implement
Coffee's quality and I song need to implement get songs
Okay we implemented public
Reemployment of PC
Stop let's Implement for console we also have console
Card game console I mean console we need to implement
Three of them but instead of PC graphics version console
Okay let's put that into behind
Under that one we have
Console
Instead of PC we have to say console right
Let me make all of the PC to console
Okay we currently have console
We also need to implement let's say mobile for this game
Unless implant mobile
For mobile you're already understand or guest
It has to be public class unless Tdap
Okay instead of console it has to be mobile right
This has to be mobile and this has to be a mobile
We completed credit card
Abstract on concrete
Products we have controls Graphics sound we have PC
Concrete products let me call it and let's call it as
PC
We also made that for console and also mobile and after the concrete product
What we have to do we have to implement
Abstract Factory
On in our abstract Factory let's define
Are interface public interface and I want to call that is
Hi game
Platform
I'm done
We need to say this every game platform
Factory
Me too I controls need
I graphics
And also need
I sound right
Let's say we have get controls
We have
Get graphics
Broadcast
Graphics
We have
Sound we have to get all of them
Okay let's do the app
We have abstract Factory it means we need concrete factories and less implement
Concrete
Factories
Another concrete factories
You're already understand I guess we need public class we have a PC
Stop being a PC
Game Factory and this has to be inherited or I game platform Factory
Of course you have an hour because you didn't Implement them less Implement them
We have to that
Public right
All has to be public by the way
After that we have to implement
Get controls and we need to say near
PC control for that right
PC control
PC control PC controls
Are you stupid controls and it has to be new
PC graphics
Graphics
And the last one has to be
PC songs
Songs
Three concrete products we need
Play Factory is on how we can do that of course coffee past let's do that
Instead of PC I want to use console let me
Right console
Okay okay okay okay okay in Harrington's PC game Factory
PC game Factory
I want to implement
Console
And it means does PC has to be console
On this PC all PC has to be console right
Kazar console is using console
And we have the last one and it has mobile right
Instead of console it has to be mobile
It means I already
Console has to be at mobile right
Do you say Wayne employment are three Factor
Is so we need a client called an address
The last step before cast are called
We need that client called and our client called has to be public class
Last qualities game details on this game details
Like the previous ones
Let's say we have a public static
Warriors
Display
Features what we have to do in this one we have to give
Game
Platform Factory and it has to take off Factory
And after do that you I guess
Understand what we will do we have we will say controls equals
Get controls as to be
Okay I will use I game platform here
Sorry
Turn on it has to be
Does cats controls right we need War reliable
Graphics
I need has to be a factory
Cats graphics
We have lost one variable sound and it has to be Factory
Songs
Okay after that I'm only printing in a real case most probably you need to make
Game platform only
Let's write a very understandable
Control controls we are cleaning only the variables
Controls
Batman clothes that
Okay okay Mom
Controls
Cats control type
Get control type Wireless discount control type
Get controls or get control
Play how cats control
Get control
Are cat control
We have yet control type
Get control type right because it's
Factor get controls for returning your eye control
What's the
Okay we have to do that for three of them right instead of controls I made that for
Graphics and
Graphics type I guess
Get Graphics quality sorry
Another one has to get sound quality
How many set of control that has to be graphics and this has to be sounds right
We completed our structure and lights on the radar
And I will explain the quote again maybe your confused
Some point
Let's say we are painting PC game
Features and SPC game features
We have to only need to make game details
We have a game details static methods and this game details
I said display features and I am giving a new pc
Game Factory
NCR I'm giving PC game Factory
I'm only I will do that for three of them
Advil
Little complex at the first
Why are you okay and you will see we are using same structure for every abstract Factory pattern
Console game features and we have
Mobile game features and this has to be
Console
And this has to be
Mobile
At the beginning writing the structure is a little hard but you can't think if you
Feature you have another virtual reality game platform and you only need
Implant
The future
Virtual reality game Factory and also the medicine
Ask finish up man you don't need to change all the car
Did you see oh my gosh we didn't care about monster oh my gosh
Let me fix the PC graphics PC sound okay
What is Kingdom we have a keyboard mouse for PC quality
Hi
Resolution
On the get sound quality let's use stereo for our
We in console I am using Gamepad last say gamepads
Game
That's too beautiful like that I guess
Okay for graphics last call Gamepad Graphics can be a standard right
Standard
That's okay you can sing another thing
In the game pass we are using for
Sound on the last one let's say in the mobile we are using
Screen
Right on the last day
Mitre resolution
Of course we have high resolution in the Mobile Spot we are simulating behavior and we have mon
Songs we are only one
For that one let me run okay
Put write new line
Like
Turn on a game
Okay we have PC game features right we have keyboard mouse on our controls graphics for high resolution
Graphics control
For our console we have Game Pass standard and so on we have touch screen meter resolution of mono
Did you see the pattern
We have abstract products I control side graphic designs we have concrete products and also abstract
The I game platform Factory here
And the last one the client called is eternity class to Showcase of unique features of games
Download for different platforms
I want to set
If the game development company decides to produce games for a new platform and like I said virtual
They will just create a new set of concrete products and a new Factory without changing the car
Increase in
Virtual reality
This flexibility alarms for easy extension and end caps list platform
Thank you for watching