Hello
Creative colors
Our front yard
Trying to connect two pieces of hardware
In those cases
An adapter comes to rescue right
Today
We are going to explore the equivalent in the realm
Program
The adapter
Pattern
What exactly is the adapter pattern
Imagine
You have got a pair of headphones
With a 3.5 mm Jack
Put your new phone
Only has a usb-c port
That's a bummer
Not if you have an adapter
Similar
The adapter pattern work as an entire media
That convert one interface
Internal
Enabling components with incompatible interfaces
The communicate
Also let's talk about characteristics
The adapter pattern has defining attrib
Primarily
It transforms the interface of a class
Enter another information
That client
On
Much
A headphone
Adapter that permits you to connect
Traditional 3.5 mm Jack 2
Are you a special
Is fossil said it facilitates
Cooperation between classes
It's just
Your headphones on your new phone
Let's talk about benefits
Is Android box of
Adapter pattern
Like that's handy adapter in your Tech driver
The adapter pattern also comes with
Is the advantages
And also this address
Promos
Compatibility
The adapter pattern ensures
Describe Enterprises can work together
Seamlessly
Is life just like your headphone adapter
Some music on your new phone
Second
And houses
Flexibility
The adapter pattern like your Tech adapter
What does flexibility by enabling different classes with
Incompatible interfaces to collaborate
And yes it's not always from on sale
First throwback additional complexity
Ask carrying
Multiple adapters for different devices can be
Florida
The adapter pattern cannot complex to your caught
Introducing more classes
Overuse
Just like how
Relying on multiple adapters cannot detangled Mass
Overuse of the adapter pattern
Turn result in
That's hard to manage
Another
Let's talk about
Why should we consider the adapter pattern
Let's return to our technology an
Find interfaces are Miss Matched
As you will use an adapter to bridge
Mismatch attack Enterprises
The adapter pattern comes in handy one two incompatible interfaces
Need to work together
Using bicycle
Just like using an adapter to connect an old gaming console
Play new TV
Adapter pattern can be used to integrate
Older
Non-compatible cord into your system
Integrating
Start party libraries
Using an adapter to connect peripherals from different manufacturers
The adapter pattern is useful
One integrating
Third party River
What's the weather in compatible interfaces
NPR Podcast
Developing plugin Arch
Much like how are Universal power adapter
Tesla says the use of devices from different countries
The adapter pattern is beneficial
In developing applying architecture
Need to add hair to the interface
Buy host application
Enabling
Platform functionality
As an adapter can help your devices function work while the adapter pattern can be
Did they cry
Common interface for system
Calls across different
Platform
Is an amplified understanding of the adapter
Like a horse style adapter
Is essential tool in the program in landscape
Is to enhance compatibility and flexibility
If you have any questions are bus
Don't hesitate to drop them in the questions
And ask for section
I am here to assist you
If you are finding the course beneficial
Please
Arabia or
Your feedback is the voltage that energy is
Bother contact
Cheap progressing throughout the
I want it of knowledge has a rights on her
Surely don't want to
Turn off
Thanks for being a part of the decision folks
Keeps flowing
See you
Are next less