We will talk about adapter
Design pattern implementation
Alaska considered a scenario where your application is integrating with
Different weather apis in is very common usage of adapter pattern
Imagine one provides
Data in Json format
The other provides data in
XML format
However
Your application is designed to work primarily
Does seamlessly integrate Water Pass without making extensive changes to
You can use adapter puzzle and lattice Implement that
Parsley
We are
Like to say the expected
Jason
CarMax Enterprise
Turn off flashlight
We have a public interface
Let's call it by Jason
Weather
Pearl weather and this is Jason weather provider
Yes
Return
Strange last say I just don't like expected okay
Weather
Jason okay
Will I say we have a first API on our
Play P by directly
Pro wise
Weather
Weather in Jacksonville Florida and also I will put all of the calls into resources
You can check after the lesson
Remember or you
You can try to run
Wake me up so you can
Coffee pot in dotnet federal and make some changes extensions and you can test
Jason Weather Service and it is inheritance from that one
Of course we will not making a call tort API we will return
Play Beethoven that way you can understand
Pattern
Main purpose is not
Implementing an API call we are trying to understand concept
Let's return Jason formats
Stream we have a temperature
That's very basic one last day we have with it is returning the temperature now
Play in our cast to 292 we also the Apple Store returning to condition
I want to say it is sunny
In our case
After that
In this case we don't have any problem because our Jason mother service
Is expecting that Jason format and it is returning Jason
We also have a letter says second API
API
And this API
At 7:00
I'm passing Cartier
We have a second API
Does API
Pearl lights
Pro wise
Weather okay weather in
Example format
Maybe in your case it can be another form
We are returning Polly clothes
Exam
Let's play crate or fake email
Weather
Service do you see the problem
Don't forget design patterns is
Good Solutions maybe the best Solutions
Very common software engineering problems for explaining all the problems is the
Best way to understand it
We eaters get weather
Instead of get weather Jason
It is get weather
Examine
And pointless say
Does get water exam
Is returning
Eczema
What is returning examine format data and you know in the XML
We
Like this one
We are using
This format for XML
Too much
It does not
Do you have to
Complete that like this
And we also copypasta as well
And we also have a condition right
We have condition
Why is this giving you a ride I don't know
Weather condition
Add this
Close condition we don't need whether we don't need
Temperature here
Together temperature weather temperature condition
But we have
Clothes that in here
Weather temperature closed conditions and condition cost okay
I'm done we have a problem
The problem is we have to convert our exam out from
Isabel Weather Service to Jason right we don't want to change our old
Hold on still we want to work
What does
API
Lattice
Adapter into game and we are it has to converse
Is Jamal
Examine weather Las Vegas Nevada service
You will see how we
Solve the problem to Jason
And we have a public
Is a mile
Jason
Weather
Adapters
We are inheriting from that
Did you see
We are
Behaving or is a mi Weather Service as a this format
If we are getting that in this format we have to implement that one right otherwise it will
On this case
Lotus say we are getting
How to give the service as a reliable hair
Dependency injection for that but I will not die into that
Read only
Let's say we have
Example Weather Service
In here
Ed
Weather Service
In our Constructor
We are inherit
Start crying that
Jason adapter
Weather Service as a parameter
And I am assigning
What's the weather right now
On the examine Weather Service has to be
But in get weather Jason
Last night in get weather this weekend we can't give a parameter here if we can give parameter Maybe
How tall is as a perimeter we can maybe
Make another ThinkPad we have to let's say
Presentation by the way in the real world you would like to use the exam out
Jason conversion library at his existing
Wilton Library is by the Bay
Pause currently
Strange
Is a male data will come into this one and we can get this data like
Example
You have to add convert to Jason logic here
Are caught
I'm not adding that to make
Play to keep that simple and returning that one
I'm done we have a two a p on vrb
We are simulating
Sorry we are inheriting board of down from I just saw my Jason weather provider
I am behaving examine with adapter like at this one
If there's like Jason leather service
Example Weather Service is
Behaving like
Jason Weather Service
Lattice
Radar
Test
We need to adjust some water provider for sleep right
Let's call
Jason Torres and his Jason service
You're already
Guess I guess new
Jason
Let me improve
Increase the size Jason Weather Service
On this Jason Weather Service right line
They are only calling Jason Weather Service
Get the weather Jason
On wheels
Jason service directly
Jason Jarvis
I only I also oh my gosh how many parentheses is iOS
In a little later I decided to use the other one
We have an exam
Example of Weather Service right
Last call
Weather Service
And it has to be new XML
What is our eczema Weather Service
Weather Service
I want
Jason weather provider
Adapter I want to create that
Farting
Example to Jason adapter I am giving this one as perimeter
I'm done you will see
Adapter
Jason mother provid
I did some other provid
I got a i Jason weather provider
Adapter
Start yet weather Jason
Use adapter
Okay that's wrong
And maybe
Okay both are returning to the same thing and let me explain the quote one by one
We firstly have a I just another provider
And this is an interface
Our application Xbox right which includes that match to get weather today in Jason format
I'm done we have a Jason Weather Service
It represents the first API and which direction provides the weather radar in Jason form
I'm done we have an example Weather Service
And we have a problem because represent the second API and each it provides later in
Choose all this problem we have eczema out to Jason weather adapter and these are electrical
It takes an instance of XML Weather Service
Unemployment I just some other provider interface
Inside the get whether Jason method it covers is a later to Jason and the client
Can I
Can you use the boat services interchangeable right with Hardware in care about their
The adapter pattern ensures that consistent interface for the client
Why are you abstracting away the complexities of data transformation
This is how you can implement
Adapter pattern for