Hello everybody what is continue our
Wet abstract Factory pattern
The abstract Factory pattern
Is a creation of design pattern
That provides an interface for creating families of related or dependent
We thought specifying their concrete crosses
That's actually
It involves multiple Factory methods and one for each type of object to
Like the fact that I'm at pattern unless you is real or an example to demonstrate this and suppose you are designing
Can you also interface tool kit on you want to support
Different times or
Like Lifetime on dark time you most probably familiar with this light and dark time concept
Each time will have its own version of compounds right
Like such as bottoms and windows
Create our product interfaces like the factory method or product
Is there facilities is important right and we have
Button productive interface and we can create that public interface
I button right we are creating interfaces with
Hitman's Enterprise by the
We want to only Implement while it's running out of here and this way
Pandora has to be implemented every
Products right
We also have a we are creating care
We are simulating
The U
So we need an interface for
I win the right and desire window has to
The abstract method of that is why it display right
Display the window
We have to create concrete products
It is
Family are what the
Previous
We have to implement lifetime
Components
Dark time compounds right how we can do that let's firstly create a public
Close
Juanita light
Bots on the right
Let me make that
Like
I need that I button inheritance here
I hope you are familiar with inheritance if you don't I put that document for that please read
Probably can I say will it rain there we are implementing
Are interface because it is a concrete clause and if you
For
What
Turn off the what concrete means
Play Street my PDF
Okay we are rendering
Light time
Button of course I will not render that rendering is not our purpose here our purpose
What is implement
Abstract Factory Pat
If we have a like button also we need the last say
Light window right we have to implement Light Window
Andy's light window has to come from I window and instead of render we are displayed
On instant of rendering we can't say this playing
And after that lettuce Implement both of them
Sorry
Both of them for dark
If we have light we also need dark and let's make that dark
Okay it has to be dark
Brandon dark times like dark time but right
Like
We need an abstract Factor here
Will you come into abstract Factory and it is very important point of
Creating abstract Factory
Falsely
Let's create an interface declaration for creation math for family of related products and
Define this interface for Sleep interface
UI
Let's say Factory
Me how are you I factory
Factory
Need tomatoes first one is I button
Alright we have to create
According to the selection of the time and also we need a window
When the
Let's continue with concrete factories we have a abstract Factory
We also need concrete factor for creating lifetime
Components last
We have
Public clothes
Light time Factory
On this public last time Factory has to inherit from
Play you I farted
In the real case it will be in different
Fathers of course but we are showing how it is working so it is in
But if
You are implementing in real life
You have to put them into
Interface folder Services folder according to your structure or according to your
Country music for desk
Okay I want to check something okay
I am recording no problem
Okay we need to implement public I button create button right
I also need to implement
What's
I bought them right button has to return
Like button right we already implemented your life
Sorry light button
Also we need to implement public
La
Island dog crate window right
It has to
Return what it has to return
Lights
Window
After that we have to do that for dark time right
You're already maybe yes
You need to implement that for dark one and
Area light has to be dark
Let's make that
And after this stop
We implemented everything
So we need to implement
We need to test our code how we can do that
Client
IUI
Let's copy past Thursday I am creating my
Are you a factory
Weather is this okay
Let's create parsley
Factory
And it is equals
Maybe you already realized that the difference from the previous Factory pattern we are not
And it has to be light term Factory right
And after that
I am creating a button and is I button is the light button and this light button
Tom Factory
Okay we have a problem here or not light on 53% can give that to us
And also I want to create a i window and can I can do this with lights
Window
It has the light window right
Anita has to be a lifetime Factory
Start
Window right
Okay we have a problem with this lifetime 5:30 what is the problem
Typo
After I cried the time
What's that
Reliable like a
What's the weather
Let me check
Okay there is a problem here
Okay let me firstly call the methods and I will check the problem again
I am using random attitude
Why is giving suggestions
Interesting Light Window
Has to be display right
Light time Factory
Create button
Lights on Factory
Are you a factory
Knock knock someone let me run
Lights on Factory is there a reliable
Let's check again and again lifetime Factory
Public class right light on Factory is a public place
Are you a factory
Okay it's correct we have a i button and I win now
Public
Is is
Public cross darktown Factory coming from IUI Factory is public Enterprise
We have abstract factories
Yeah that's interesting man
I don't see any problem
Let me write all the code on
Check after that
Instead of light I am using dark
We have many dark button and also a dark window
Dark window
Call sah
On dark time Factory has to be that has to be
I need has to be dark Town Factory
Okay we are using now
The problem is that
While calling you can't realize the problems mostly like that
Don't stop why
Are sure there is no problem
You have very small and nothing not too important problem but
We can't see in the first look
Why you run it you can see
Are rendering light on display light turn button rendering dark thumb button and displaying dark
The pattern almost having multiple Factor men's rights
In our case best for creating buttons and windows may be other
It allows creating families of light objects like you are compounds of time
We don't need to specify their concrete classes
Saw this decomposed decline called from concrete class right
We are the coupling
From the concrete classes
And what that's why
New York Times or components
Creation is very easy and the main difference from the previous
Factory Patronus we don't give any
And this is how you can Implement a u
Enterprise with abstract Factory pattern thank you for watching