Hello everybody and looks like you
Pattern coatings
What's the last make a small introduction for Baylor pattern
Step by step creation of complex OB
Using the correct take care of actions
The construction process
Can world
Different representations
I don't surprise that high level of control
Over the assemble of the projects
We will restrict that with a fun example we are creating a character for
Role playing video game we are calling them mostly As RPG
Play where's my have an option to customize their characters appearance
Habit
Let's see how we can use the Builder pattern
Translate
We have a product firstly
And that's product
Please keep attention to this commands it as giving you blueprint
How are implementing are
Patterns we have a RPG character for sale
This RPG characters role playing game and it is RPG character
Let's define the character
Start with we have hair
Okay
We have let's say strange
We have armor
On arm
Let's also make public
I will add Guitar Centers
Don't worry about that
We have a we
It's good we have three of them and you know we have yet
And set
All of them
So you don't need
It has to be
Let me
Yes
We are adding that for all of them
Okay the RPG character has three variables hair armor and weapon
Let's continue
Lights at only one method we will not add a message for strike
Connect to our healing
But we are only showing the characters
To do that
I'm making glass set public white show function
Add this troll function letters make that bigger than the shell function
Basically making
Cancel that rightline
I am parenting the
Character only we are only simulating RPG game character right
Can we have a hair here and I want to show that
So I only need to give
Hair reliable
I can't
I asked
I have three more right two more sorry
On let's
We have a arm
I'll ask you armor and we have a weapon and it has weapon
Oh my gosh I don't need them
I guess it is okay
Turn off the bat
Okay what's the problem
Unexpected character open
No man it is expected character
It has to be expected one we don't need this too
We need a builder here
Faster than other ones and maybe easier
We have a public
Abstract
Bass clef
For our character
Play alarm
And we have that
Matilda
Parsley
We have a protect
Do you know what protected means
It means
Let me ride on Xbox Live
Characterize RPG character okay
And we have a character
Only the
Which are inherited from this one
Can access this variable if we make this public everybody can access that
If you make it private
Only the this class can access that but if you make it protected
Only the classes which are in hurting from
This one can access this where I will
We have at least a public
Wyatt
Create character
Character
Character character character ideas
Okay that's great character is only a tiny car reliable
Sonya RPG
Character right
Okay and we have need to get methods
Let's say public
Wyatt
Jets
Characters
We have to do that because if we want to access
Outside of the class it is a protected variable
So we have to return that
Character
Okay that's perfect
It's not
Wyatt has to be this
Let's say our bullet point or Bass class have three other
Call them abstract
Wyatt let's say Sad hair
Set
We have we need tomorrow right
Off instead of hair
Last call
Armor and last call
Whip
Reaper
We have
Are we have a builder sorry let's call it abstract Builder
And when you see an abstract you have to implement concrete walls right
You I guess understand that or memorize that
Concrete boiler we need to implement
Unless Implement our concrete Builder and others the important point
We have last say
Two characters
One is for warrior and one is for Mega Builder
Do you know also period executor is can't be calling in role-playing games
Last employment public class
Are warriors
Warrior I guess it is yeah that's why I got gas
Boiler and if it is a warrior wheeler and it has to be correct right
Only we have to implement what we have to implement we have to implement all
Turn off this
Say and it has to be not
Abstract
I am using one line functions I am on the same character
The character is inheriting from here
Did you see
Equal
Well I say
Short for that's why
I will also Implement others
Oh my gosh I forgot forgot
Short instead of air I am saying armor
And I am saying weapon sorry
Unless say we have a plate
Armor here and also we have
SWAT for a character
It is
Has to be over right right
All right all right all right
Why we have to do that all right
Because otherwise
Let me show you
Otherwise it will give an error
The mill
Otherwise at the new Kmart because
Highest inherited member said hair weave that is abstract and you have to override them
PDF for
And also did you see I can access this character
But if
Let me show you
If I try to let it
Do that and show you how
It will give an error
Set hair
We thought that one
Okay radio
Weather
Did you see the name character doesn't exist in the current contacts
Because we are not in hurting from that one is a protected variable of our character bear
If we have a wireless at another one and let's call it
Me
The mega maid sorry not Mega it's Mitch Mitch Miller and let's
Play in the match hair is long
Let's do clock rope for them
Last us stock for that
Knight online maybe you are a familiar
RPG games
Some of them is
Light on 9067
Time in Tacoma
Question I asked for the What is the
RPG games you know or play it
And you can understand the quote by the way
Remember your
Game and how is the variables and also you can
Make that bigger
Builder we are creating a character creator and his character creator
Builder is that
Private and we have to set this track we have to create let's say character creator
Spell tractor
No man it is greater
Character on this character creator getting a character well
As that arguments and we are
Creating this dot Weller equals well right
And let's
Play character how we can create character
What's the ER
Do you have a public storage
Character and this great character Methodist creating a character
On our character
Oh my gosh
I'm making lots of typos and we are only will The Great Character and then
Setting all of them right after that
Set timer
Let's say we are not
Armor lights at all of them
Play all about
VIP
And we have to implement we have to get this character right so I'm arguing here
Okay it's disappearing public
We have to get this character RPG character
Characters
Does say it will return RPG character what are RPG character
Let me copy past and then get character
Andy's got character me
Omni has
Return are builders
Try not to get characters
I'm done let's come into
Use case I'll show you how the cartwheel works we have
Radio weather right and we have to create
Radio
Weather
Mega
Builder
And this has to be
Mega
Weather
We are creating a creators
And this is
Character creators right
Character creators
Crater on
Giving my radio Builder
I'm done
Maria Bell
Oh my gosh I made that very very
Interesting way
Let me copy
I made last
Oh my gosh it's correct
I also we have a makeup wielder match Builder not Mega I am still saying
Change the alarm
And we have two new character crater
Okay
Life is creators
Create character here
Call Ryan is has to be come from crater
Create character not create character yet character
Let's say radio
Start shop
It will show you are right right
When I run
Hair short armor play timer on weapon in the new case I decide
To create
Max Builder I have to say
Let's say whatever
I don't need
I am not
Creating a new arrival
I am giving Mega Builder here
And I
What's match Builder not Mega Man
It has to be matched
Match
This has to be
New Management
Let me run
Did you see let me explain the code again
We made lots of things
But let's explain one by one we have a product
RPG character
And this represents the character in the game right with attributes hair
Armor and VIP
We have a Cracker Barrel
Taco Bell
Provide the necessary abstract Mass to set attributes on a RPG character for that
And we have a warrior and also made trailer
These are concrete Builders these are the concrete implementations of builder of our
Character build
And this class us
To Define ordinary which attributes should be set for an RPG character
In a simple example
The order doesn't matter but in more complex scenarios maybe you have to set some of the things with
I'm using this setup
For a game RPG game
Play us can choose between predefined character bills
Are the game can easily introduce a new character class
We thought changing the college
You can maybe implemented assassin build
With only
Implement
Similar
Disney
If you decide to add a new character Maybe
Like I said
Or I guess Archer or Rodger is a very common ones with simply
Add concrete Builder and I am talking about concrete Builder like that one
And for that character we are entering flexible and extensible system and nobody need to
Watch Maine builder for creating a Archer Builder
And this is how you can Implement RPG game
Assimilate RPG game oh my gosh okay